import 'package:quiz_app_tutorial/models/question.dart';

const List<Question> sportsQuestions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. In which sport would you perform a slam dunk?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Tennis',
      'b) Soccer',
      'c) Baseball',
      'd) Basketball',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. Who is considered the "King of Clay" in tennis?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Roger Federer',
      'b) Novak Djokovic',
      'c) Rafael Nadal',
      'd) Andy Murray',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. What is the home stadium of FC Barcelona?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Anfield',
      'b) Camp Nou',
      'c) Santiago Bernabeu',
      'd) Old Trafford',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. Who holds the record for the most Olympic gold medals?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Michael Phelps',
      'b) Usain Bolt',
      'c) Simone Biles',
      'd) Nadia ComÄƒneci',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 2018?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Brazil',
      'b) Germany',
      'c) France',
      'd) Argentina',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. Who is the all-time leading scorer in NBA history?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) LeBron James',
      'b) Kareem Abdul-Jabbar',
      'c) Kobe Bryant',
      'd) Michael Jordan',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. Which golf major is played at Augusta National Golf Club?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) The Open Championship',
      'b) PGA Championship',
      'c) U.S. Open',
      'd) The Masters',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. Who is the current Formula 1 World Champion?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Lewis Hamilton',
      'b) Sebastian Vettel',
      'c) Max Verstappen',
      'd) Fernando Alonso',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '9. In which year did the first modern Olympic Games take place?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) 1896',
      'b) 1900',
      'c) 1920',
      'd) 1936',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '10. Who won the 2021 Wimbledon Women\'s Singles title?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Serena Williams',
      'b) Simona Halep',
      'c) Ashleigh Barty',
      'd) Naomi Osaka',
    ],
  ),
];
